### PATHIK MODI

### Full Stack Software Developer



### CONTACT

- NZ Permanent Resident
- modipathik95@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/ pathik-modi
- www.github.com/pathik-modi
- https://datingapppathik-3e22183e1486.herokuapp.com/

### **PROFILE**

Self-driven technology enthusiast with an appetite for solving business challenges. My experience during a fast-paced administrative role at a large organisation and performancedriven e-commerce role at a SME have taught me to take ownership of my work and overcome business challenges while being resourceful, curious and driven. After years of interest and self-learning, I decided to take a plunge into programming and have been hooked ever since. I am excited to bring my fresh perspectives and problem-solving skills to contribute to a dynamic team.

### .NET CORE & ANGULAR

Built a full-stack dating app with .NET, SQLite/PostgreSQL & Angular architecture. Deployed with Docker on Heroku. See live link above.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER Dev Academy Aotearoa, Auckland

July 2023 - December 2023

- Completed the immersive 17-week, 800+ hour NZ certificate in Applied Software Development.
- Gained exposure to agile methodologies with a team of 12 devs during group projects, pair programming and work-place simulating multi-day projects.
- Built a full-stack mobile-first web app within a team
  of 4 from conceptualisation, design to development
  with a tight deadline of 7 days. The app features
  authentication using Auth0, a statistics dashboard
  using Chart.js, a QR code scanner and more.
- Learned to build full-stack web apps using JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, React.js, Tanstack React Query, Knex.js, Tailwind CSS, REST APIs, Express.js, SQLite3, Auth0.

# DIGITAL MANAGER & DIGITAL ASSISTANT Shut the Front Door, Auckland

March 2020 - July 2023

- Delivered on core KPI of e-commerce revenue growth by 220% year-on-year.
- Started as digital assistant in 2020 and got promoted in 2021 reporting directly to the Director.
- Took ownership of the online customer experience including design, content, navigation, information architecture, marketing & functionality.
- Develop a data-driven paid advertising strategy with continuous improvement on core KPIs such as: improving online conversion rates, increasing AOV (Average order value), reducing abandoned carts, reducing bounce rates.

### **SKILLS**

.NET | Angular | C# | Docker TypeScript | JavaScript | React.js Node.js | SQLite | PostgreSQL Express.js | HTML | CSS

### **EDUCATION**

# MASTERS OF COMMERCE - GLOBAL MANAGEMENT & INNOVATION

**University of Auckland** 

March 2017 - October 2018

Group project with Dr. Juliet
 Ansell, Innovation Leader - Health
 & Nutrition division from Zespri
 Int Ltd, researching better
 exploration, assessment and risk-management of projects resulting
 in a balanced portfolio.

### PASSED CHARTERED FINANCIAL ANALYST (CFA) LEVEL I EXAMINATION

Results.:

http://basno.com/pf18b8z2

2016

## BACHELOR OF MANAGEMENT STUDIES

**Mumbai University** 

2013 - 2016

#### INTERESTS

Tennis | Weight Training History Podcasts | Surfing | Golf

### REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST

- Devised ecommerce growth strategy and delivered strategic initiatives through the day-to-day operational running and updates on the site.
- Took on responsibility to recruit, onboard, train and manage a digital marketing team.
- Supported the company in filling the accounting/office support position and the wholesale business manager position.
- Helped problem-solve company-wide operational challenges, including implementing a central tracker for inventory transfers to aid the online order dispatching team.

# SCHOLARSHIPS ADVISER The University of Auckland

April 2019 - March 2020

- The Scholarships Office oversees 70 million dollars in tax-free funding.
- I met the high integrity and trust requirements while managing scholarship applications, applicant data, filtering applicants meeting the eligibility criteria and processing payments.
- Demonstrated smooth stakeholder management by advising faculties, donors and students while managing a portfolio of scholarships and awards from Business school, Law school, Medical school and University-wide international scholarships.

# CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE The University of Auckland

October 2018 - March 2019

## STUDENT ALUMNI FUNDRAISING REPRESENTATIVE The University of Auckland

March 2018 - June 2018

# FLOOR MANAGER & FRONT OF HOUSE 1947 eatery, Auckland

May 2017 - March 2018